Guide to the Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
- Series II. Assignments
  - Heinz Beisdorf and Carol Staples during taping of TV show, December 1969; 108; 54 (Box 13)
  - DEA departmental activities, December 1969; 109; 103 (Box 13)
  - Cattle being judged, February 1970; 110; 32 (Box 13)
  - Guterman Lab, February 1970; 111; 99 (Box 13)
  - Canadian Expo 1968, Vic Stephens, Les Baldwin and Charlie Fisher (Dir. Turk has IAD negatives, Sheet #3), 1968; 112; 50 (Box 13)
  - Paul Synder with tange and kitchen model used in modular home, March 1970; 113; 204 (Box 13)
  - Food Science lab screenings, March 1970; 114; number missing (Box 13)
  - Environmental chambers containing 15 birds each used for studying various methods of handling poultry, March 1970; 115; 18 (Box 13)
  - 1970 Agriculture Leader's Forum, March 26, 1970; 116; 166 (Box 13)
  - Agent's in depth conference, March 1970; 117; 223 (Box 13)
  - Water Sampling Station, Aurora Experiment Farm, April 1970; 118; 94 (Box 13)
  - ETV at Henry St. John's School, April 1970; 119; 68 (Box 13)
  - Backyard Chicken coops, May 1970; 120; 58 (Box 13)
  - Home Economic Institute, April 1970; 121; 46 (Box 13)
  - Institute of Food Science and Marketing Forum, April 4, 1970; 122; 79 (Box 13)
  - Extension Director's Forum on Environmental quality, May 1970; 123; 39 (Box 13)
  - International Agriculture--Philippines (Director Turk has all photos and negatives from this job. 5/74), June 1970; 124; 40 (Box 13)
  - Bees shipped by mail from Florida to Cornell, June 1970; 125; 64 (Box 13)
  - Human Ecology Graduation--1970, June 1970; 126; 48 (Box 13)
  - Vision (making slides), April 1970; 127; 91 (Box 13)
  - Children's storage devices, Spring 1970; 128; 37 (Box 13)
  - Legislative Tour, June 29, 1970; 129; 357 (Box 13)
  - Alfalfa Weevil, June 1970; 130; 49 (Box 13)
  - Alfalfa fields and plants being handled by people, June 1970; 131; 63 (Box 13)
  - Retirement of Ethel Olson and Leigh Harden, June 1970; 132; 95 (Box 13)
  - Food Chain Industry Representatives, June 1970; 133; 25 (Box 13)
  - 4-H Leader training at Cortland State University, June 1970; 134; 231 (Box 13)
  - 1970 AAACE Convention at Cornell, July 1970; 135; 303 (Box 13)
  - Mount Pleasant, June 1970; 136; 50 (Box 13)
  - Upholstery Research Study, June 1970; 137; 113 (Box 13)
  - Paul Dean portraits, July 1970; 138; 20 (Box 13)
  - Children at the Northside House, July 1970; 139; 92 (Box 13)
  - Home Demonstration agents posing with publicity blocks for the Nursery School State Fair Exhibit, June 1970; 140; 134 (Box 13)
  - Publicity photos for Tren grape drink, June 1970; 141; 44 (Box 13)
  - Prof. Minges testing melons for maturity, Aug. 1970; 142; 20 (Box 13)
  - Polluted, blighted areas of Elmira and Syracuse, New York, August 1970; 143; 137 (Box 13)
  - Rotary Club, photos of Fall Creek, August 1970; 144; 16 (Box 13)
  - 4-H Activities, June 1970; 145; 400 (Box 13)
  - Agents in Service Training Program, June 1970; 146; 32 (Box 13)
  - Collard greens to show insect damage, August 1970; 147; 21 (Box 13)
  - Research on conservation houseboat, August 1970; 148; 77 (Box 13)
  - Foreign visitors, August 1970; 149; 20 (Box 13)
  - State Fair--1970, August 9, 1970; 150; 244 (Box 13)
  - Research at Aurora Farm, Aurora, New York, September 1970; 151; 22 (Box 13)
  - Growth chambers -- post lab (Grogen), August 1970; 152; 42 (Box 13)
  - Agronomy and Plant Breeding Field House, September 1970; 153; 34 (Box 13)
  - Apple Orchard--Rochester area, Sept. 1970; 154; 110 (Box 13)
  - Communication Arts Grad. Center, Research and Scenes, September 1970; 155; number missing (Box 13)
  - Ag. Quad, September 1970; 156; 35 (Box 13)
  - Clark Garner and Kathy Kiumijian with decorating samples, September 1970; 157; 19 (Box 13)
  - Human Ecology Nursery School, September 1970; 158; 190 (Box 13)
  - Dean Orillo visit with Director Kenneth Turk, Dean Palm, etc., October 1970; 159; 69 (Box 13)
  - Ag. Council dinner--Award to Joe King, October 26, 1970; 159A; no number given (Box 13)
  - Human Nutrition and Food Lab. Scenes, October 1970; 160; 54 (Box 13)
  - Prof. J. Camhi and Dr. Mija Hinkle in Langmuir Lab, October 1970; 161; 36 (Box 13)
  - Dr. R. D. O' Brien, Dr. Chris Wilkinson in labs, October 1970; 162; 54 (Box 13)
  - Micro-wave oven conference, October 1970; 163; 79 (Box 13)
  - 1971 State Fair--color, 1971; 164; 22 B & W, 38 color (Box 13)
  - *, 165 (Box 13)
  - Grad School of Nutrition Activities, students, faculty, etc., November 1970; 166; 100 (Box 13)
  - 4-H exhibit, January 1971; 167; 20 (Box 13)
  - Radio Studio, December 1970; 168; 21 (Box 13)
  - Retirement luncheon for Larry Zuidema in Big Red Barn, September 1970; 169; 16 (Box 13)
  - Waste Lab, January 1971; 170; 61 (Box 13)
  - ETV Center, January 1971; 171; 54 (Box 13)
  - Beef Cattle Short Course, January 1971; 172; 58 (Box 13)
  - Cold hardiness project--Floriculture, January 1971; 173; 21 (Box 13)
  - Plant Breeding activities, January 1971; 174; 327 (Box 13)
  - Farm Bureau pictures, January 1971; 175; 31 (Box 13)
  - Dinner for C. Roscoe Edlund--Donation for Video Tape Room, January 1971; 176; 11 (Box 13)
  - Colloquium Rural Housing, January 1971; 177; 54 (Box 13)
  - Puppet making, February 1971; 178; 43 (Box 13)
  - Graduate school of Nutrition pictures, February 1971; 179; 154 (Box 13)
  - Communication Arts Department activities, February 1971; 180; 826 (Box 13)
  - New York City --Brooklyn Consumer Education, March 1971; 181; 110 (Box 13)
  - Director Smith, March 1971; 182; 18 (Box 13)
  - Agriculture Leaders Forum, March 1971; 183; 24 (Box 13)
  - East Harlem, March 1971; 184; 508 (Box 13)
  - In--Depth Week, March 15-19, 1971, March 1971; 185; 38 (Box 13)
  - Pre Institute pictures--college of Human Ecology, March 1971; 186; number missing (Box 13)
  - Gov's Council of Environmental Advisors, June 1971; 187; 117 (Box 13)
  - Pictures taken for CSE exhibit in Barton Hall, June 1971; 188; 91 (Box 13)
  - Area shots of Syracuse, Tompkins and Broome County (ENEP), June 1971; 189; 451 (Box 13)
  - Arnot Forest, June 1971; 190; 70 (Box 13)
  - TITLE, DATE; Job #; NO. of Negs. (Box BOX)
  - Storage facilities at Cornell Apple Orchard, July 1971; 191; 11 (Box 14)
  - Pictures for Bulletin-Guidelines for Proper Milk Collection, July 1971; 192; 335 (Box 14)
  - Nutrition in the News exhibit and county agents, July 1971; 193; 70 (Box 14)
  - Activities at the Ag. Waste Management Lab, July 1971; 194; 205 (Box 14)
  - Borlaug's Visit, August 1971; 195; 45 (Box 14)
  - Research on burned fabric, March 1971; 196; 45 (Box 14)
  - Crop fertilization experiment in Ellis Hollow, August 1971; 197; 53 (Box 14)
  - Taken for cover of Cornell Recommends for Field Crops, August 1971; 198; 41 (Box 14)
  - Dog Show bulletin--handling dogs for breed classes, August 1971; 199; 154 (Box 14)
  - State Fair--1971, August 1971; 200; 138 (Box 14)
  - Dean Palm--FRIENDS plaque, October 1971; 201; 23 (Box 14)
  - Cornell apple orchard, October 1971; 202; 34 (Box 14)
  - Farms & rural homes, October 1971; 203; 50 (Box 14)
  - ENEP--Indian Aides from Onondaga County tour Cornell Univ., October 1971; 204; 27 (Box 14)
  - DEA fabric exhibit, November 1971; 205; 58 (Box 14)
  - Microwave oven, December 1971; 206; 24 (Box 14)
  - Retirement of Profs. Hertel and Tyler, December 1971; 207; 19 (Box 14)
  - 4-H groups at the Trumensburg IGA, January 1972; 208; 41 (Box 14)
  - Miner Institute, February 1972; 209; 36 (Box 14)
  - Student from CSE-Rochester inner--city, January 1972; 210; 35 (Box 14)
  - Ag. Leader's forum, February 1972; 211; 91 (Box 14)
  - Student teachers in Rochester, March 1972; 212; 134 (Box 14)
  - Human Ecology Institute, April 1972; 213; 220 (Box 14)
  - Lecture in Warren Hall, April 1972; 214; 27 (Box 14)
  - Martian life detection system--Adamson, Francis, Duxbury. Agronomy Department, May 1972; 215; 21 (Box 14)
  - Dean Palm's dinner, May 1972; 216; 100 (Box 14)
  - Plant stand, May 1972; 217; 17 (Box 14)
  - Harvey Pough and pond life, May 1972; 218; 40 (Box 14)
  - Ruth Jillson giving donation to Alumni Fund, May 1972; 219; 34 (Box 14)
  - New Dairy Research Center in Harford, New York, May 1972; 220; 199 (Box 14)
  - Students in Human Ecology taken for Careers Brochure, 1972; 221; 98 (Box 14)
  - Russian visitors at Morrison Hall, June 1972; 222; 26 (Box 14)
  - Stan Warren retirement, June 1972; 223; 26 (Box 14)
  - Floriculture leaders at Cornell, June 1972; 224; 20 (Box 14)
  - 4-H pictures taken for 4-H Foundation Annual Report, June 1972; 225; 25 (Box 14)
  - Nutrition on Stage exhibit, June 1972; 226; 77 (Box 14)
  - Pictures for COSPA exhibit, July 1972; 227; 60 (Box 14)
  - *, July 1972; 228; number missing (Box 14)
  - Model trailer in different stages of construction, July 1972; 229; 63 (Box 14)
  - Pictures of people in the Home Study program--Ag. Economics, August 1972; 230; 70 (Box 14)
  - Photosynthesis studies at Ellis Hollow--(Cornell Recommends), August 1972; 231; 26 (Box 14)
  - Empire Farm Days, Aug. 1972; 232; 105 (Box 14)
  - Dean Kennedy at his desk, August 1972; 233; 24 (Box 14)
  - Boy looking at tropical fish in tank, Fall 1971; 234; 19 (Box 14)
  - Prof. Romanoff and Mrs. Romanoff in offices, September 1972; 235; 53 (Box 14)
  - Art Freije--Broome County 4-H agent, September 1972; 236; 104 (Box 14)
  - Roger Morse's bee house on the Ag. Quad, September 1972; 237; 50 (Box 14)
  - State Fair--1972, August 1972; 238; 136 (Box 14)
  - Onondaga County agents at work--Ag., Home Economics, & 4-H, September 1972; 239; 262 (Box 14)
  - Family Planning Conference at Grad. Center, September 1972; 240; 214 (Box 14)
  - Shopping at Triphammer and vicinity, September 1972; 241; 190 (Box 14)
  - Prof. Grogan cross--pollinating corn, September 1972; 242; 16 (Box 14)
  - Entomology Research, October 1972; 243; 26 (Box 14)
  - Informal portraits of Donald Gannon in his office, October 1972; 244; 17 (Box 14)
  - Prof. Kosikowski & Leo Weirzdicki in Food Science Lab, October 1972; 245; 40 (Box 14)
  - Int. Seminar on farm irrigation systems in developing count, October 1972; 246; 33 (Box 14)
  - Taste panel for fresh tomatoes, October 1972; 247; 19 (Box 14)
  - Home Study staff, October 1972; 248; 31 (Box 14)
  - Beef Cattlemen Short Course, January 1972; 249; 53 (Box 14)
  - HUD in Elmira after the June 1972 flood, November 1972; 250; 70 (Box 14)
  - Herpetology collection at Langmuir Lab, November 1972; 251; 58 (Box 14)
  - Scenes around New York State taken by Conrad Von Hyning, 169?; 252; 146 (Box 14)
  - Scenes around Ludlowville and vicinity, 197?; 253; 55 (Box 14)
  - Sage Chapel Choir--Christmas presentation, December 1972; 254; 44 (Box 14)
  - Bradfield Emerson, February 2, 1973; 255; 28 (Box 14)
  - 1973 Environmental Leaders Forum, February 9, 1973; 256; 166 (Box 14)
  - Sea Grant Seminar Series, February & Mar. 15, 1973; 257; 216 (Box 14)
  - 1973 Human Ecology activities, 1973-1974; 258; 553 (Box 14)
  - First year Extension Agents in Training, January 1973; 259; 86 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Luncheon, March 22, 1973; 260; 21 (Box 14)
  - Student Projects (N.S.), April 9, 1973; 261; 25 (Box 14)
  - Exhibits, March 16, 1973; 262; 49 (Box 14)
  - 1973 Ag. Leaders Forum and dinner honoring George Trimberger, March 3, 1973; 263; 56 (Box 14)
  - Orchard (grafting), April 1973; 264; 36 (Box 14)
  - Food Science activities, April 1973; 265; 414 (Box 14)
  - 4-H Youth Program--New York City, April 1973; 266; 333 (Box 14)
  - Symposium and dinner for Dr. F. C. Steward, May 1973; 267; 102 (Box 14)
  - 1973 Human Ecology Institute, May 1973; 268; 153 (Box 14)
  - Animal Science activities, May 1973; 269; number missing (Box 14)
  - Louise Daniel and Harold Williams, May 1973; 270; 31 (Box 14)
  - Baby Peregrine Falcons--Hawk barn, June 1973; 271; 121 (Box 14)
  - Second Environmental Leaders Forum, June 15, 1973; 272; 356 (Box 14)
  - Co-op Food Store--State Fair exhibit, June 1973; 273; 13 (Box 14)
  - Agriculture and the Environment--Morrison Hall, June 1973; 274; 186 (Box 14)
  - Microwave oven and equipment, June 23, 1973; 275; 35 (Box 14)
  - Home Study Advisory Board, June 21, 1973; 276; 21 (Box 14)
  - Applying fungicide to elm tree, June 25, 1973; 277; 27 (Box 14)
  - Nassau Community aides at Cornell, June 1973; 278; 41 (Box 14)
  - Human Ecology Graduation--1973, May 1973; 279; 118 (Box 14)
  - 4-H Club Congress presentation of awards, June 1973; 280; 29 (Box 14)
  - Aerial views by Elmer Phillips, July 1973; 281; 41 (Box 14)
  - Perception experiment--Kraig Adler, Biology, July 25, 1973; 282; 40 (Box 14)
  - Agronomy activities, August 1973; 283; 147 (Box 14)
  - Martha Van Rensselaer and Liberty Tower, August 1973; 284; 34 (Box 14)
  - Meeting in Dean Kennedy's office with foreign visitor, August 1973; 285; 16 (Box 14)
  - CEPP Course 535U -- Grad course, Consumer in the Market, 1973 Summer; 286; 31 (Box 14)
  - Cutting down elm tree on Ag. Quad, August 1973; 287; 22 (Box 14)
  - Empire Farm Days, Hartford, New York, August 1973; 288; 92 (Box 14)
  - Pomology activities, September 1973; 289; 99 (Box 14)
  - State Fair--1973, September 1973; 290; 76 (Box 14)
  - Dimock Plant Pathology Lab Dedication, August 28, 1973; 291; 90 (Box 14)
  - Floriculture activities, September 1973; 292; 197 (Box 14)
  - Dr. Kosikowski using a new device for projecting notes for visuals in class (filed under Ag. College, Resident Instruction), October 1973; 293; 45 (Box 14)
  - Vegetable Crops activities, October 1973; 294; 93 (Box 14)
  - Chancellor Samonte & Dean Bernardo, University of Philippines with Dean Kennedy, President Corson and Dir. Turk (Int. Visitors), Sept. 18-20, 1973; 295; 20 (Box 14)
  - Visiting lecturer in Victor Stephen's class. Setting up a point of purchase display. (Comm. Arts--Resident Teaching), Oct. 1973; 296; 20 (Box 14)
  - Dedication of Dimock Lab (Cornell Univ.--Ded. Ceremonies), Nov. 15, 1973; 297; 24 (Box 14)
  - Photos of algae (Plant Pathology), Nov. 26, 1973; 298; 11 (Box 14)
  - View from Bradfield Tower (Campus Scenes), Nov. 1973; 299; 15 (Box 14)
  - Ag. Economics Home Study participants at Cornell University (Ag. Economics--Marketing), Dec. 5, 1973; 300; 48 (Box 14)
  - TITLE, DATE; Job #; NO. of Negs. (Box BOX)
  - Inplant control of dairy waste by Bob Zall and Jordan (Dairy Products--Research), Dec. 1973-Jan. 1974; 301; 166 (Box 15)
  - Innovative Teaching Programs--College of Agriculture (Resident Teaching--College of Agriculture), Dec. 1973; 302; 107 (Box 15)
  - Elfriede Abbe, Science Illus. Genetics (Portraits--A), Jan. 24, 974; 303; 36 (Box 15)
  - Fly breeding areas in barns (Entomology--Research), Feb. 1974; 304; 55 (Box 15)
  - Chrysanthemum micro-propagation (Floriculture--Research), Feb. 1974; 305; 38 (Box 15)
  - Prof. W. Keeton & Mel Kreithen with pigeons (Press Photos), Feb. 1974; 306; 60 (Box 15)
  - The Talking Flower (Exhibits), Mar. 1974; 307; 103 (Box 15)
  - Grace Hilt--Cooperative Extension--Roberts Hall interview Richard McCaffey for a gents position. Purpose--Recruitment Brochure (Organizations--Extension service & County Agricultural agents at work) David Call, Director of Extension, at his desk. (People--Portraits), 308; 460 (Box 15)
  - Human Ecology Institute--1974 (College of Home Economics), May 1974; 309; 247 (Box 15)
  - Environmental Leaders Forum (Cornell University--Activities), Apr. 1974; 310; 188 (Box 15)
  - Professor Fred Lechner with "Plant Grower" he designed, May 16, 1974; 311; 25 (Box 15)
  - Mite research and Toxological research (Entomology--Research), May 1974; 312; 50 (Box 15)
  - Visual workshops for ENEP aides around New York State (Extension--Agents in Training), May 1974; 313; 228 (Box 15)
  - Nutrition Institute--1974 (College of Home Economics), June 1974; 314; 91 (Box 15)
  - Bulletin board design--simple bulletin boards (Art work), May 1974; 315; 71 (Box 15)
  - Debeaking, position of bird, after debeaking (Poultry), July 1974; 316; 23 (Box 15)
  - Rural Sociology--Creative Dance (Rural Sociology), July 5, 1974; 317; 37 (Box 15)
  - 4-H Cub Congress, June 1974; 318; 201 (Box 15)
  - Human Ecology faculty, June 1974; 319; 891 (Box 15)
  - Food Executive Program (Res. Teaching--Ag. College), June 27, 1974; 320; 56 (Box 15)
  - Presentation of Japanese garments to Human Ecology Costume Collection, June 1974; 321; 30 (Box 15)
  - Simulation of "In-Depth Week" workshop on long-range planning (Extension--Home Economics--agents at work), June 1974; 322; 30 (Box 15)
  - Research on product in reading--Prof. George McConkie (Press), Aug. 1974; 323; 35 (Box 15)
  - Cornell Home Study Program (Ag. Economics--Marketing), July 1974; 324; 51 (Box 15)
  - State Fair--1974, Aug. 1974; 325; 285 (Box 15)
  - Carrol Project photos (Visual Aids--Equipment), 1974 Spring; 326; 20 (Box 15)
  - Gov. Wilson's visit to Vet College and Animal Science Teaching and Research Center at Harford, New York (People--Groups, General), Sept. 4, 1974; 327; 123 (Box 15)
  - Photos used as illustration for Extension Review Magazine (Extension--Editorial Office), Sept. 4, 1974; 328; 28 (Box 15)
  - Two biology students studying animal behavior (Press), Sept. 6, 1974; 329; 27 (Box 15)
  - Vision--Spring, 1974--Screen Printing (Art Work & Vision), Oct. 3, 1974; 330; 74 (Box 15)
  - Course description picture of Home Study staff, Course Catalog--1975 (Ag. Eco.--Marketing), Sept. 23, 1974; 331; 18 (Box 15)
  - Egg Cholesterol reduction (Poultry Research), Oct. 1974; 332; 30 (Box 15)
  - Studying reproductive hormones. Dr. Hansel, Dr. Hixon, D. R. Gengenbach (Sheep--Research), Oct. 1974; 333; 20 (Box 15)
  - Kerry Kerr--Human Ecology student (Press), Oct. 1974; 334; 50 (Box 15)
  - Award to Gertrude Armbruster from microwave oven organization for her research (Cornell University--Awards), Oct. 1974; 335; 20 (Box 15)
  - New fish products developed by Poultry Science from flounder rach. (Poultry Science & Sea Grant Research), Oct. 1974; 336; 30 (Box 15)
  - Human Ecology activities (College of Home Economics), Nov. 1974; 337; 178 (Box 15)
  - Chinese Delegation (Foreign Visitors), Nov. 1974; 338; 55 (Box 15)
  - Youth Community Action Conference (HDFS--Research, Teaching), Nov. 20, 1974; 339; 68 (Box 15)
  - Grant to Poultry Department (Press), Nov. 18, 1974; 340; 23 (Box 15)
  - Meat stretching (Cornell University--Activities), Nov. 25, 1974; 341; 62 (Box 15)
  - Director of Research, Ag. College, Cornell University, Noland Van Demark (People--Portraits), Dec. 1974; 342; 60 (Box 15)
  - *missing*, 343; No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 344, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 345, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 346, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 347, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 348, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 349, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 350, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 351, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 352, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 353, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 354, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 355, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 356, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 357, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 358, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 359, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - 360, No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - *missing*, 361; No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - Chrysanthemums infected with virvids (Plant Pathology), May 1975; 362; 55 (Box 15)
  - Small indoor bulbous plants (Bulletins), May 1975; 363; 56 (Box 15)
  - Microwave oven research (Food & Nutrition Research--Nutrition), May 1975; 364; 79 (Box 15)
  - 1975 tour of dairy farms in western New York, May 1975; 365; 37 (Box 15)
  - Highway School--1975 (Press), June 1975; 366; 43 (Box 15)
  - Dr. Pechuman with Mr. Schmidt and collection he is donating to Cornell University (Press), June 1975; 367; 19 (Box 15)
  - Prof. Lisk studies on uptake of heave metals by plants. Don Lisk feeding pelelized paper to sheep., June 1975; 368; 93 (Box 15)
  - Congressman Peyser visits Cornell University (Press), June 1975; 369; 18 (Box 15)
  - Different varieties of Allium (Floriculture--Allium), June 1975; 370; 40 (Box 15)
  - Alumni breakfast at North Campus (Cornell Univ. Activities), June 1975; 371; 44 (Box 15)
  - Professor Evelyn Stout with needle point presented to her by two of her students (Cornell University--Presentations), June 1975; 372; 12 (Box 15)
  - Ice cream sandwich research (Dairy Products--Ice Cream), June 1975; 373; 22 (Box 15)
  - Project of Carl Schrofield--Natural Resources--Effect of acid rain on sucker fry, also Natural Resources repairing seine (Nat. Res.--Research), June 1975; 374; 21 (Box 15)
  - Dedication of Vegetable Crops Building, Freeville New York, named for Homer C. Thompson (Cornell Univ.--Dedications), July 1975; 375; 82 (Box 15)
  - Photos of wheat, alfalfa, oat and timothy varieties with plant breeders (Plant Breeding), July 1975; 376; 48 (Box 15)
  - Herb Everett--Director of Resident Instruction at his desk, July 1975; 377; 35 (Box 15)
  - Campus Scenes, July 1975; 378; 136 (Box 15)
  - Pat Brecht--Vegetable Crops working on a variety of tomatoes that will not ripen; Biology lab. Students dissection of pigs, July 1975; 379; 129 (Box 15)
  - Growing plants in soil mixed with waste paper, Don Lisk at Guterman Labs (Farms--Farm Waste Disposal), Aug. 1975; 380; 12 (Box 15)
  - Campus Master Plan Book (Aerial Views), Aug. 1975; 381; 91 (Box 15)
  - Field tests of metabolic activity of snap beans (Plant Breeding & Vegetable Crops), Aug. 1975; 382; 28 (Box 15)
  - Cucumber varieties being bred for resistance to virus (Plant Breeding), Aug. 1975; 383; 18 (Box 15)
  - Photos show aphid traps (cages) on potato leaves. Testing for resistance to aphids (Plant Breeding and Entomology), July 1975; 384; 16 (Box 15)
  - Testing responses of pigs to unusual stimuli as affected by diet (Swine--Research), July 1975; 385; 17 (Box 15)
  - Photographs showing the differences between sprayed and unsprayed apples (half grown mackintosh) (Bulletins), Aug. 1975; 386; 5 (Box 15)
  - Compost piles, center pile was built in the fall of 1972, left hand pile, 1973, right hand pile, 1974 (Bulletins), Aug. 1975; 387; 11 (Box 15)
  - Plants in Ozone Chamber, testing for resistance to air pollution (Plant Breeding), Sept. 1975; 388; 21 (Box 15)
  - D. DeJong showing how to inspect beehives (Entomology), Sept. 1975; 389; 24 (Box 15)
  - Testing resistance of corn seedlings to aluminum (Veg. Research), Aug. 1975; 390; 24 (Box 15)
  - Human Ecology Forum (College of Home Economics), Sept. 1975; 391; 27 (Box 15)
  - 1975 State Fair exhibits, Human Ecology and Ag. College, Aug. 1975; 392; 113 (Box 15)
  - Ludgate's Vegetable stand on Hanshaw Road & Eddydale Vegetable stand on Elmira Road (Bulletin), Sept. 1975; 393; 64 (Box 15)
  - Entomology laboratory scenes--sorting insects (Res. Teaching), Sept. 1975; 394; 37 (Box 15)
  - Costume Collection at MVR (Press), Sept. 1975; 395; 50 (Box 15)
  - Windows for student financing at Day Hall (CU Buildings), Oct. 1975; 396; 21 (Box 15)
  - Photos taken for Ag. College Bulletin--Education Department, Oct. 1975; 397; No. of Negs: (Box 15)
  - Sheet 1 & 2: David Kitt Farm, Oct. 1975; 397; 73 (Box 15)
  - Sheet 3: BOCES Center, Elmira, New York, Nov. 1975; 397; 13 (Box 15)
  - Sheet 4: Robinson & Carpenter, Bishops Hardware, Nov. 1975; 397; 32 (Box 15)
  - Genetic resistance of potatoes to leaf hoppers. Ward Tingey, Freeville farm (Plant Breeding and Entomology), Oct. 1975; 398; 28 (Box 15)
  - Plots with different varieties of corn, (Plant Breeding) and testing corn seedlings for resistance to aluminum, Oct. 1975; 399 (see job 465); 41 (Box 15)
  - Sheet 1: Entomology field trips (field trips, lab scenes for Ag. School), Oct. 1975; 400; 30 (Box 15)
  - Sheet 2: Soil testing machine, Oct. 1975; 400; 7 (Box 15)
  - Sheet 3: Biology lab in Plant Science building, Oct. 1975; 400; 13 (Box 15)
  - Sheet 4: Vern Rockcastle's Education class, Oct. 1975; 400; 37 (Box 15)
  - TITLE, DATE; Job #; NO. of Negs. (Box BOX)